legacytexas.com 2014-07-12

# LegacyTexas | Privacy Statement

#### OUR PRIVACY PLEDGE TO YOU

As our customer you provide us with important information about yourself. We believe it is our responsibility to safeguard your personal and financial information. While some financial institutions share account owner information with other businesses, we are committed to keeping it confidential.

We have developed the following privacy policy to ensure you the confidentiality you deserve. You have our promise that we will adhere to these guidelines. It is our pledge to you.

#### NOTICE OF YOUR FINANCIAL PRIVACY RIGHTS

We, our, and us, when used in this notice, mean LegacyTexas Bank.

This is our privacy notice for our customers. When we use the words “you” and “your” we mean the following types of customers:

* Our customers who have a continuing relationship by purchasing or holding financial products or services such as a(n):

  * Deposit account
  * Loan account
  * Safe deposit box
  * Self-directed Individual Retirement Account

We will tell you the sources of the information we collect about you. We will tell you what measures we take to secure that information.

We first define some terms.

Nonpublic personal information means information about you that we collect in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. Nonpublic personal information does not include information that is available from public sources, such as telephone directories or government records. Hereafter, we will use the term “information” to mean nonpublic personal information as defined in this section.

An affiliate is a company we own or control, a company that owns or controls us, or a company that is owned or controlled by the same company that owns or controls us. Ownership does not mean complete ownership, but means owning enough to have control.

A nonaffiliated third party is a person we do not employ or a company that is not an affiliate of ours. This is also known as nonaffiliated third party, or simply, an “other party.”

#### THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT

We collect information about you from the following sources:

  * Information you give us on applications or other forms
  * Information about your transactions with us
  * Information about your transactions with other parties
  * Information from a consumer reporting agency
  * Information we receive as a result of verifying customer information

#### THE CONFIDENTIALITY, SECURITY, AND INTEGRITY OF YOUR INFORMATION

We restrict access to information about you to those employees who need to know that information to provide products or services to you. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to protect this information.

#### YOUR INFORMATION AND OUR AFFILIATES

We may disclose information about you to our affiliates.  Examples of affilates include, but are not limited to, LegacyTexas Insurance and LegacyTexas Title.

#### YOUR INFORMATION AND OTHER PARTIES

We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in this policy or as permitted by law. Examples of this might include disclosures necessary to service your account or prevent unauthorized transactions.

#### INFORMATION ABOUT FORMER CUSTOMERS

We do not disclose information about former customers, except as permitted by law.

#### AUTHORIZED SHARING – JOINT MARKETING

We may disclose the following information to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements:

Information you give us on an application or other forms, such as:

  * Name
  * Address

We disclose the information listed above with other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements. You do not have a right to opt out of the disclosure of this information.

Types of Businesses

We may disclose information pursuant to joint marketing agreements to the following types of businesses:

Financial service providers, such as:

  * Private label credit card issuers

Reasons for Disclosing

We may disclose information about you to other financial institutions with whom we have joint marketing agreements to provide you with information about additional products and services.

#### STATE LIMITATIONS

AL, AK, CA, ID, and VT – We will not share this information about customers who reside in Alabama, Alaska, California, Idaho, or Vermont.

MA, MS, and NJ – We will not share any information derived from deposit relationships with us about customers who reside in Massachusetts, Mississippi, or New Jersey.

IL – We will not share this information about our customers who reside in Illinois with other parties.

#### TEXAS NOTICE

This institution is chartered, licensed, or registered under the laws of the State of Texas and by state law is subject to regulatory oversight by the Texas Department of Banking. Any consumer wishing to file a complaint against this institution should contact the Texas Department of Banking.

LegacyTexas Bank also engages in the business of selling checks as an agent for a company licensed under the laws of the State of Texas and subject to regulatory oversight by the Texas Department of Banking. Any consumer wishing to file a complaint concerning sale of check activities should contact the Texas Department of Banking.

Consumers may file complaints with the Texas Department of Banking by contacting the Department through one of the means indicated below:

  * In Person or U.S. Mail: 2601 North Lamar Boulevard, Suite 300, Austin, Texas 78705-4294
  * Telephone No.: 877-276-5554
  * Fax No.: 512-475-1313
  * E-mail: [consumer.complaints@dob.texas.gov](mailto:consumer.complaints@dob.texas.gov)
  * Website: [http://www.dob.texas.gov](http://www.dob.texas.gov/)
